Guide to the Goddard-Riverside Community Center Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Executive Director Files, 1960-1994
  - Subseries IV.2: Bernie Wohl
    - Biographical Information, 1972-89 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Camp, 1973-78 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Camp Management Project, 1975-77 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work, 1978-79 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Committee for the Heights Inwood Homeless, 1983-84 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Committee for the Heights Inwood Homeless-Proposal, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Community Board #7, 1976-82; 1986-90 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, 1973-74 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Community School Board, 1973-78 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1972-90 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Dromenon Theater, 1979-80 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Homeless Video, 1982-83 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Hotel Preservation Corporation, 1980-81 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Hotel Preservation Corporation, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Hotel Preservation Corporation, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Hotel Preservation Corporation, 1984-85 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Interface, 1980-82 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Interface, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Interface-Enterprise Committee, 1982-83 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Interface-Training Manual, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Legislation, 1972-75 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1972-74 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1975-77 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Neighborhood Committees, 1973-85 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - New York State Association of Settlement Houses and Neighborhood Centers, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - New York State Association of Settlement Houses and Neighborhood Centers, 1975-76 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - New York State Association of Settlement Houses and Neighborhood Centers, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - New York State Association of Settlement Houses and Neighborhood Centers, 1983-85 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Papers and Speeches, 1969-88 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - South Side Settlement: Administration, 1962-68 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - South Side Settlement: Administration, 1970-72 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - South Side Settlement: Camp, 1971-72; [n.d.] (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - South Side Settlement: Netherlands Film Project, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - South Side Settlement: United Community Council, 1966-March 1967 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - South Side Settlement: United Community Council, May 1967-1969 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, 1972-April 1973 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, May-December 1973 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, January-June 1974 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, July-December 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, January-June 1975 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, July-December 1975 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Strykers Bay Neighborhood Council, 1976-78 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Tenants Association, 1970's-80's (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Tenant & Community Management Corporation, 1975-November 1976 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Tenant & Community Management Corporation, December 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Union Negotiations, 1982-89 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Report #1 Part 1, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Report #1 Part 2, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Report #2 Part 1, 1966-67 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Report #2 Part 2, 1966-67 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Report #3, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Final Report Part 1, 1965-66 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Final Report Part 2, 1965-66 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Final Report Part 3, 1965-66 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - United Community Centers-Juvenile Delinquency Project: Final Report Part 4, 1965-66 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - United Community Centers-"Laboratory for Change,", [nd] (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, January-June 1973 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, July-December 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1978-79; 1982-83 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - West 87th Street Block Association, 1976-83 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - West Side Assessment Center, March-July 1981 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - West Side Assessment Center, August 1981-82 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - West Side Cluster, 1976-77 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - West Side Cluster, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - West Side Cluster, 1979-83 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - West Side Cluster, 1984-85 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - West Side Cluster, 1989-90 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - West Side Task Force For Youth, 1979-80 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - West Side Urban Renewal Area, 1975-77 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Youth Board-Committees and Conferences, 1978-83 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Series V: Stephen Russo Files
  - Association for the Advancement of Social Work with Groups, 1987-89 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Camp Wel-Met, 1987-89 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University School of Social Work-Field Work Advisory Committee, 1988-90 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University School of Social Work-Field Work Students, 1984-85 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    [ ***RESTRICTED***]
  - Columbia University School of Social Work-Field Work Students, 1986-87 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Medical Center, 1983-91 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Department of Mental Health, 1989-90 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Department of Mental Health, 1990-91 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Food and Shelter Program, 1987-89 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Foster Care, 1988-89 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1983-86 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1987-90 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1985-87 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Hunter College-Field Work Students, 1989-90 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Intergenerational Program, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - New York Book Fair for the Homeless, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - New York Book Fair for the Homeless, 1988-90 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - New York State and City Funding, 1987-89 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Nicaragua Sister City Project, 1987-88 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Phelps House, 1984-91 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Senate Hotel, 1988-90 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Senior Center, 1983-86 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - United Neighborhood Houses-Housing Committee, 1989-91 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - West Side Ad Hoc Committee Against Crack, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Youth Programs, 1988-Feb 1989 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Youth Programs, March-September 1989 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Series VI: Programs and Activities
  - After School-Youth Board Contracts, 1979-80 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - After School-Youth Board Contracts, 1980-81 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - After School-Youth Board Contracts, 1981-82 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Annual Activities Presentation, 1971-73 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Camp: Administration, 1970-87 & [nd] (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Camp: Alumni Lists, 1934-77 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Camp: Larry Baker, 1975-76 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Camp: Budgets, 1966-84 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Camp: Brochures and Schedules, ca. 1960-85 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Camp: Camper Evaluations, 1973-79 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    [***RESTRICTED**]
  - Camp: Camper Evaluations, 1982-84 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Camp: Camper Lists, 1969-83 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Camp: Camper Publications, 1970-88 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Camp: Camper Statistics, 1971-77 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Camp: Childrens' Letters and Petitions, 1970-77 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Camp: Construction, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Camp: Correspondence, 1959-70 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Camp: Correspondence, 1971-72 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Camp: Correspondence, 1973-77 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Camp: Correspondence, 1978-88 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Camp: Hospital Camp Project, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Camp: Older Adults-Plays, 1972-74 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Camp: Older Adults-Programs, 1971-78 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Camp: Older Adults-Programs, 1979-84 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Camp: Peer Group Leadership Program, 1970-75 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Camp: Planning and Development, 1961-75 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Camp: Reports, 1968-82 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Camp: Sixty Plus Camp, 1966-69 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Camp: Staff, 1967-80 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Camp: Staff Evaluation, 1973-77 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Camp: Staff Manuals, 1965-76 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Camp: Staff Manuals, 1977-88 & [nd] (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, 1964-67 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, Jan-Jun 1968 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, Jul-Dec 1968 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, Jan-Aug 1969 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, Sept-Dec 1969 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, 1970-71 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, 1973-76 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Camp: Umbrella Program, 1978-89 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Camp: Woodworking Shop, 1976-77 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Camp: Work Projects, 1976-79 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Employment Training Act, 1975-79 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Creative Arts, 1966-73 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Creative Arts, 1974-84 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Creative Arts, 1985-89 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Day Camp, 1967-77 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Day Camp, 1989-90 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Day Care, 1964-69; 1983 & [nd] (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Education, 1976-77; 1988-89 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Family Service Program: Administration, 1983-88 & [nd] (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Family Service Program: Allerton Coalition Team, 1988-89 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Family Service Program: Cases 001-009, 1984-85 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Family Service Program: Cases 010-018, 1984-85 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Family Service Program: Cases 019-029, 1984-85 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Family Service Program: Cases 030-041, 1984-85 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Family Service Program: Coalition for the Homeless, 1985-88 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Family Service Program: Council of the City of New York Select Committee on the Homeless, 1986-88 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Family Service Program: Emergency Alliance for Homeless Families and Children, 1986-89 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Family Service Program: Field Work Students, 1986-89 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Family Service Program: Interfaith Committee on Homelessness and Housing, 1985-87 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Family Service Program: Partnership for the Homeless, [nd] (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Family Service Program: Partnership for the Homeless-Cases, 1985-88 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Family Service Program: Reports, 1984-87 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Family Service Program: Resource Materials, 1983-89 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Family Service Program: Youth Worker, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Head Start, 1966-69 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Head Start, 1970-75 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Head Start, 1976-77 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Head Start, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Head Start, 1979 & 1989 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Flyers, 1963-1989 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Program Reports, 1960-74 & [nd] (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Operation Friend, 1972-75 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Options, 1984-88 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Options, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Peer Group Leadership in Drug Abuse Prevention, 1973-77 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Play School, 1962-64 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Program Planning, 1973-75 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Program Reports-New York City Housing Authority, 1970-80 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Program Statistics, 1962-70 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Project Reachout, 1979-83 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Project Reachout, 1985-91 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Project Reachout-Contracts, 1979-80 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Project Reachout-Contracts, 1981-82 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Project Reachout-Contracts, 1982-83 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Project Reachout-Contracts, 1987-88 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Project Reachout-Contracts, 1988-89 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - School Programs, 1961-64; 1985-90 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - School Programs-Joan of Arc, 1981-1989 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Senior Center, 1968-71 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Senior Center, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Senior Center, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Senior Center, 1974-84 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - SRO Law Project: "Certificate of Need...,", 1990 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - SRO Law Project: Contract, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - SRO Law Project: Correspondence, 1980-88 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - SRO Law Project: Flyers and Announcements, 1982-83 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - SRO Law Project: Rapsheet, 1982-84 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, 1973; 1980-82 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, January-August 1983 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, September-December 1983 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, January-June 1984 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, July-December 1984 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, January-April 1985 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - SRO Law Project: Reports, May-August 1985 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Sixty Plus Club, 1962-67 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Summer Program, 1965-77 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program, 1985-89 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Vacations for the Aging, 1961-74 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Work Study, 1965-78 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Youth Board: Proposals and Contracts, 1967-70 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Youth Board: Proposals and Contracts, 1976-80 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Youth Board: Reports, 1976-80 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Youth Board: Proposals and Contracts, 1980-81 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1981-82 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1982-83 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Youth Board: Proposals and Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Youth Board: Proposals and Correspondence, 1984-85 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1984-85 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1984-85 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1985-86 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1986-87 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Youth Board: Correspondence and Reports, 1987-88 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1988-89 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Youth Board: Contracts, 1989-90 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Youth Education in Action, 1969-70 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Youth Education in Action, January-May 1971 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Youth Education in Action, June-December 1971 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Youth Education in Action, 1972-74 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Youth Programs-Publications, 1979-89 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Youth Project: Contracts, 1976-78 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Youth Project: Correspondence, 1976-77 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Youth Project: Proposal, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Youth Project: Proposal, 1977-78 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Youth Project: Proposal, 1977-78 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Youth Project: Proposal, 1977-78 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Youth Project: Proposal, 1978-79 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Youth Project: Reports, 1976-September 1977 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Youth Project: Reports, October 1977-September 1978 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Youth Project: Reports, October 1978-1980 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Youth Project: Cases (A), 1976-79 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Youth Project: Cases (B), 1976-79 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Youth Project: Cases (C), 1976-79 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Youth Project: Cases (D), 1976-79 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Youth Project: Cases (E), 1976-79 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Youth Project: Cases (F), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Youth Project: Cases (G), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Youth Project: Cases (G), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Youth Project: Cases (H), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Youth Project: Cases (J), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Youth Project: Cases (K-L), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Youth Project: Cases (M), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Youth Project: Cases (N-O), 1976-79 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Youth Project: Cases (P), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Youth Project: Cases (P), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Youth Project: Cases (R), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Youth Project: Cases (R), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Youth Project: Cases (S), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Youth Project: Cases (S), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Youth Project: Cases (T-V), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Youth Project: Cases (W-Z), 1976-79 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Youth Services Agency-Applications, 1971-76 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Youth Services Agency-Reports and Correspondence, 1970-76 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Series VII: Audio-Visual Material
  - Subseries VII.1: Drawings
    - Architectural Drawings: Camp, 1973-75 (Box 1)
    - Head Start Senior Center, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Subseries VII.2: Audio Tapes
    - Child Study Association of America/Wel-Met Inc.-Conferences-Today's Family, 1976, (Audio tape, ) (Box 97)
    - Child Study Association of America/Wel-Met Inc.-Conferences-Rights of the Child, [nd], (Audio Tape, ) (Box 97)
    - Corporate Stamp-Child Study Association of America/Wel-Met Inc., [nd], (Stamp, ) (Box 97)
    - Corporate Stamp-Riverside Community House, [nd], (stamp, ) (Box 97)
    - Wel-Met Camps, [nd], (Pennant, ) (Box 97)
  - Subseries VII.3: Photographs
    - Wilson Industrial School for Girls, ca. 1900 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Wilson Industrial School for Girls, ca. 1910 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Riverside Day Nursery, ca. 1900 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Child Study Association of America: Benefit Performance, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Child Study Association of America: Board Members (Group), 1940s-60s (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Child Study Association of America: Board Members (Individual), 1920s-60s (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Child Study Association of America: Children, 1953-54 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Child Study Association of America: Children's Center, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Child Study Association of America: Conference, [nd] (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Child Study Association of America: Conference, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Child Study Association of America: Head Start, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Child Study Association of America: Nurse's Training, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Benefit, [nd] (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Building, 1940s-50s (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Camping and Day Trips, 1940s-60s (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Children, 1940s-60s (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Miscellaneous, 1940s (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Performances, 1940s-60s (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Staff, 1940s-60s (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Teens, 1930s-60s (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Negatives, [nd] (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Slides-Annual Report, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Wel-Met Inc., 1960s (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Riverside Community House, 1940s-50s (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Activities, 1969-86 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Animals, 1969-85 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Arrivals and Departures, 1969-85 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Campers, 1967-72 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Campers, 1973-85 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Contact Sheets, 1970s-80s (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Dining Hall, 1967-85 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Lake Scenes, 1968-76 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Miscellaneous, 1969-85 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Outdoor Scenes, 1972-85 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Performances, 1972-85 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Renovations and Construction, 1967-85 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Senior Citizens, 1969-81 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Sports, 1971-85 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Staff, 1968-85 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Swimming Pool, 1971-85 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Wel-Met, 1986-87 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Camp-Winter Scenes, 1969-83 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Children, 1967-80s (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Cleanup Projects, 1959,1976 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Contact Sheets, [nd] (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Exhibits-Mounted Pictures of Programs Staff and Activities, ca. 1960s (Box 298)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Exhibits-Mounted Pictures of Programs Staff and Activities signed by Helen Harvey Shotwell, ca. 1960s (Box 299)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Homelessness, ca. 1980s (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Miscellaneous, ca. 1960s-80s (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Miscellaneous, ca. 1960s-80s (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Operation Friend, 1960s (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Options Program, 1980s (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Performances, 1960s (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Phelps House Dedication, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Phoenix Project, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Preschool, 1970s-80s (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Senate Hotel, 1980s (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Seniors, 1980s (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Staff, 1960s-80s (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Teens, 1959-80s (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Youth Project, 1970s (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Negatives-Camp, 1970s-80s (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Negatives-Housing Projects, 1980s (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Negatives-Miscellaneous, [nd] (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Negatives-Programs, 1980s (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Slides-Camp, 1961-85 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Slides-Camp Wel-Met, ca. 1970s (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Slides-Miscellaneous, 1960s-80s (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Slides-Phelps House Dedication, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Goddard-Riverside Community Center: Slides-Performances, 1970s (Box 104, Folder 9)